Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Materials, 1985-2017; 485634
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: New York Building Foundation, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593436 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Nominating Committee, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593437 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: PAC, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593438 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Policy and Advocacy, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593439 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Publications, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593440 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Past Videos, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593443 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 1994-1997 (Box 60)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 1998-2001 (Box 61)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 2002-2004 (Box 62)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 2005-2008 (Box 63)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 2008-2010 (Box 64)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 2011-2013 (Box 65)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Daily Planners, 2014-2016 (Box 66)
  - 2017 Accretion: Membership Directories, 1982-2012 (Box 67, Box 68)
  - 2017 Accretion: Legislative Bulletins, 1970s (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 2017 Accretion: Nominating Committee, 1950s-1970s (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 2017 Accretion: Luncheons, 1980s (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 2017 Accretion: Task Force for Review of NYC Governmental Procedures Relative to Construction, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 2017 Accretion: Awards Luncheons, 1997-1999 (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
  - 2017 Accretion: Industry Recognition Dinner, 1997-2016 (Box 69, Folder 7-9)
  - 2017 Accretion: NYBC Annual Reports, 2001-2010 (Box 69, Folder 10-11)
  - 2017 Accretion: Trade Publications, 2009-2015 (Box 69, Folder 12-17)
  - 2017 Accretion: Responsibility on Construction Jobs, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - 2017 Accretion: Subcommittee of Building Industry Practices, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - 2017 Accretion: Correspondence, 2012 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - 2017 Accretion: The Impact of the Current Insurance Industry Crisis on NYC's Construction Industry, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - 2017 Accretion: Builders of New York, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - 2017 Accretion: Richard T. Anderson Photos (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - 2017 Accretion: Photographs, 1994-2016 (Box 69, Folder 24-26, Box 70)
  - 2017 Accretion: P.S. 147 Plaque, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - 2017 Accretion: Video Recordings of NYBC Events, 2002-2011 (Box 71, Box 72)
  - 2017 Accretion: Board of Education Award, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 2017 Accretion: Newspapers, 1971-2017 (Box 73, Folder 3-4)
- Series IX: Archived Website, Mar 14, 2009-ongoing; 547018
  The New York Building Congress, founded in 1921, is a coalition of 400 constituent organizations comprising more than 250,000 skilled trades people and professionals that works to advance economic and infrastructure investment and job creation. The Congress publishes reports and analysis related to building projects in New York City. The Congress also created the New York Building Foundation, which promotes research, education, and philanthropy in the construction industry. The website contains reports, committee and council information, and event listings.
- Series X: Richard T. Anderson Papers, 1980-2015; 2 linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  This accretion to the New York Building Congress Records (dated 1980-2015) consists of materials created and collected by Richard T. Anderson, former NYBC President and Director Emeritus focused on RTA Advisory Services. Materials in this series include correspondence, NYBC meeting agendas and minutes, reports from annual NYBC membership meetings, newspaper clippings on topics concerning urban spaces and construction, and materials related to Anderson's professional relationships with adjacent organizations. The bulk of this series consists of transcripts of remarks given by Anderson before municipal bodies and other interest groups concerning subjects such as urban planning, re-zoning and development, public transportation, and specific New York City buildings, such as the New York Stock Exchange and the Javits Center expansion.
  - Richard T. Anderson Papers, 1980-2015 (Box 58, Box 59, Box 73, Folder 1)